嗨，最近过得怎么样？这里是Dave2D
hey how's it going, Dave2D
华硕C302，这是他们的Chromebook，
this is the ASUS C302, it's their chromebook,
他们的顶级Chromebook，
their top-of-the-line Chromebook,
我在这个频道上没有发过多少关于Chromebook的报道
and I don't do much coverageof Chromebooks on this channel,
至少我以前没有，因为我觉得这种类型的硬件，Chromebook，
at least I haven't in the past because I feel like this type of hardware, Chromebooks,
他们的价值特别依赖于他们的软件
their value is highly dependent on their software
如果没有一个很好的软件体验，这个整个系统不能很好地工作，
like without a good software experience this whole ecosystem doesn't work very well,
而且过去一直做到没有很好，但最近，
and in the past that has been great but recently,
实际上在不久的将来，这些将变得非常棒。
actually in the very near future these will become awesome.
所以，在我开始全面评论这个特例之前
So, before I get into the whole like review of this particular
我需要谈一下Chromebook在2017年初的状况。
unit I need to talk about the state of Chromebooks in early 2017.
Chromebook传统上就是这样
So Chromebooks have traditionally been just like
好吧，如果你不知道Chromebook是什么东西
ok if you don't know what a Chromebook is,
它是一个便宜的笔记本电脑，像个设备，
it's a inexpensive laptop like device,
基本上可以认为它是一台笔记本电脑，
well it's basically a laptop,
它运行Google制作的Chrome操作系统。
and it runs Chrome OS which is a software made by Google.
现在，为了把这些东西应用于传统的东西
Now, in order to put applications on these things traditionally
你点开一个叫做Chrome网上应用店的东西
you go to something called the Chrome Web Store
这有点像他们的应用商店，就像苹果手机有app store，
which is kind of like their app store so iPhones have the app store,
安卓手机有google play store，
android phones have the google play store,
Chromebook曾经拥有这种东西，叫做Chrome Web Store
Chromebooks have .they used to have, something called the Chrome Web Store
这是他们的应用程序库。
which is their application kind of library.
问题在于，开发人员对ChromeWeb Store的开发工作并没有太大的发展
The problem was that developers just didn't develop much for the Chrome Web Store
大多数受欢迎的应用程序在Chrome网上应用店中不可用
like most of the popular applications weren't available on the Chrome Web Store
所以谷歌去年做了这个事情，就像“嘿
so Google did this thing last year whether like 'hey
我们将允许Android应用程序，
we're going to allow Android applications,
就是你会在你的安卓手机上看到的那些，
the ones that you would see on your android phone,
我们将在不久之后把它们放在Chromebook上”
we're going to put those on to Chromebooks in the near future'
那就是现在。
and that is right now.
在接下来的一两个星期内，他们将在大多数Chromebook上推出
In the next week or two they're going to be rolling out across most Chromebooks
至少在所有的本代和次代Chromebook上
at least all of the current generation one and future generation Chromebooks
他们将能够运行Android应用程序。
they're going to be able to run android applications.
所以乍一看，这不是一件大事，是的，就像一堆应用程序，
So at first glance it's not like a huge thing, yeah it's like a bunch of apps,
正在进入系统，但这真的是在改变游戏规则。
are coming into the system but this really is a game changer.
所以现在你不是仅拥有一个巨大的应用程序库，
So not only do you have just a gigantic library of apps now,
你现在可以离线做东西了
you're now able to do stuff offline so
所以如果你想离线编辑文件，
if you want to do editing of documents offline,
如果您想要下载视频，你想离线玩游戏
if you want to play games offline if you want to download videos
离线观看netflix的内容，您现在可以在Chromebook上做这些
and watch stuff off netflix offline you can now do this on a Chromebook,
这些都是基本上是成熟的电脑。
these are basically full-fledged computers.
所以这些安卓应用程序添加到这个chromebook系统里
So the addition of these android apps into this chromebook ecosystem
我认为这将严重影响Android平板电脑的销售和生存。
I think it's going to heavily affect the sales and the livelihood of Android tablets.
这是一个Galaxy Tab S3，出来一周了，也可能是两周，
This is a Galaxy tab S3, came out a week maybe two weeks ago,
我觉得这些产品在到货时就死了。
and I I feel like these products are dead on arrival.
我的意思是，为什么你会买这些，用一半的价格
I mean, why would you purchase that when you could buy these for half the price
他们就好像不如那些能力更强。
and they're just as if not more capable than those.
有些应用程序不工作，如VSCO Cam，
Some apps don't work yet, like VISCO Cam,
这是一个非常受欢迎的照片编辑应用程序，当我尝试安装它，
this is a really popular photo editing app, and when i try to install it,
它说这是不兼容的，如果你最喜欢的应用程序现在不可用，
it says it's incompatible but chances are if your favorite app isn't available right now,
将有一个别的可选择的，甚至两个或十个可用，
there's going to be an alternative or two or ten
并且可以在Chromebook上运行。
that are available and able to run on Chromebooks already.
所以一般来说，我觉得如果你是普通用户
So in general, I think if you are an average user
我的意思是我知道有很多我的观众，
I mean I know a lot of my audience are like,
他们是重度的玩家，或只是照片或视频编辑;
they're heavy gamers or just photo or video editors;
如果你是其中一人，那么你可能无法使用这个
if you're one of those people then you probably won't be able to use this
就像你唯一的机器，也许像一个次要的设备，
as like your only machine,  maybe as like a secondary device,
但对于大多数人来说，您可以使用Chromebook;
but for most people you can get by with a Chromebook;
App Store的选择非常丰富
the App Store selection is huge,
所以是的，我认为这只是Chromebook的状态。
so yeah I thinkt hat's just the state of Chromebooks right now.
所以我想谈谈具体的设备。
So I want to talk about the device in specific now.
所以这是华硕C302
So this is the ASUS C302
我个人认为这是现在最好的Chromebook;
and personally I think this is the best Chromebook right now;
这很贵 - 这是五百美元，
it's expensive - it's five hundred dollars,
我想让我们先来谈谈我最喜欢的事情。
and I guess let's talk about the things that I do like about first.
它质量很好 全铝建造，
So it's got great build quality; full aluminum build,
一切都是坚实的 - 设备上没有塑料，
everything is solid - there's no plastic on the device,
从铰链到完成的一切都像顶级设备一样。
everything from the hinge to the finish feels like a top tier device.
There is like you can see over
here that it wasn't milled from a single
block of aluminum there's like two
pieces that they put together, but the
build quality on this thing is quite
good. There's two USB-C ports and there's
no USB-A ports - obviously not a huge
selection of ports, but it's a Chromebook
and you probably won't be connecting too
many devices to this thing. You also have
your microSD slot and then on the other
side you have your volume rocker, power
button and audio jack. The screen is
2400 x 1340 - it's reasonably bright and color
accurate, I'd say it's about average for
a higher end laptop or Chromebook. There
are better screens out there but I like
this one a lot. Performance is pretty
strong - strong enough I mean for what you
would do on a Chromebook - I can easily
have 10 chrome tabs open with Spotify,
Netflix or Twitch running in the
background and it'll handle it with ease.
The 64 gigs of storage feels a little
light, especially if you're coming from
laptop, but you can easily add a microSD
card if you want. I will say though if
you're interested in purchasing this thing,
I would highly recommend getting the
upgraded one, like the one with the core m
processor - I've used the Pentium
processor and it feels noticeably slower.
It's not that much cheaper so I highly
recommend getting the upgraded version
with more storage and a faster processor.
Okay let's talk about the keyword.
This is why I've crowned this ASUS as the
best Chromebook. It's backlit 1.4
millimeters travel, perfect layout,
there's really nothing I would change
about this keyboard. Maybe like the
springs could be a little bit stiffer
but really it's a great keyboard, it
feels a lot like the macbook air, and for
what I use a Chromebook for and what I
think is a lot of people will be using
Chromebooks for - the typing experience
has to be awesome and this really nails
it. Very few Chromebooks do. And so
there's another competitor to this that
I would consider to be like the
second-best Chromebook out there which
is the Samsung chromebook plus, but the
keyboard on that is significantly worse
than this, that's why I prefer this.
The other thing that I really liked about
this like device as to why I think it's
the best - it's the flip. So a lot of
devices, when you flip it into tablet
mode, it's just not a comfortable device.
This thing is relatively light - 2.6 pounds (1.18kg),
but it's also the ergonomics like
when you hold this thing it feels like
an actual tablet, and I think if you're
going to have a 2-in-1 device if your
tablet mode your tent mode and your
laptop mode are all really comfortable
to use you've done a good job.
The trackpad is less awesome - surface feels
good, but it lacks perfect precision -
you'll get the occasional jitter, it is a
decent trackpad though. The battery life
is great - it's a 39 watt hour battery,
you'll comfortably hit eight or more
hours on this thing, so I've been able to
hit eight hours with the screen at 250,
keyboard backlighting on, I mean it's a
Chromebookm it's not pulling too much juice so
it's going to last. It also uses USB-C
charging - if you have other USB-C devices
that's a nice bonus. The speakers are
also decent; they're positioned nicely,
you get a good stereo effect, and they're
clear enough - there's no fan noise on
this thing so audio comes out pretty
clean, but it's a small speaker on a
Chromebook so it's not going to be
amazing. There's a few things I don't
love about this Chromebook - I wish the
screen was brighter, 300 nits is fine for
indoor use but if you bring it outdoors
it's not ideal. The other thing are the
bezels - so, these bezels are, I mean
they're not huge or anything but when
you have it in
tablet mode, especially because you have
that ASUS logo on the side, it doesn't
look like a particularly elegant screen.
I wish these bezeles were smaller but
that's about it, there's really not much
I dislike about this Chromebook. Now, it's
not cheap, it's five hundred dollars
which is actually quite expensive for a
Chromebook, but in 2017 you're not going
to get this kind of build quality unless
you're paying this kind of money. So is
it worth it? I think it is, especially if we
consider the android apps that are
coming in - if you can make this fit into
your workflow, I think this is a really
good device. Hope you guys enjoy this
video, thumbs if you liked, subs if you
loved it, see you guys next time.